Fabia the first brought you know after
a burger with our job to go at it with
that and I've been back here after an
argument only when you know what party
of them are you but are there for four
exclusively if they like party I.V.
Or if Iraq is going to be a generic
party of the second party candidate or
a great party very bad fact that all of
you try to have an education and campaign
here but I don't write it out there I did
I thought I did I thought you are correct
that you are not going to
party here now to. Actually.
Party about right after
a good week everybody and I don't
have to. Read all of your comedy.
Until I get it down to right
well it's
a room anyway Joe better
than that but there's the minor
complication of the rant
thank inventories. Assets.
Fly abilities not prospects.
Well that's the list weight is one asset
you miss the paternal watch that takes
away your life minute by minute. There's
a liability in it that to you she resigned
from the dream she wasn't so dumb you
are
a self-appointed bum. Thare look here are you
shedding an old fashioned tear you don't
cry in holidays you live or die in our day
things could be tough and after all an
artist has suffered I guess it must be
a grain of Italian dust left over from your
last campaign I'll put it down to ride
straight flick it just
a real mess you're all mixed up snap out
of it get yourself fixed thievin Oh it's
misbehave they always remember to say
thank you what's the matter of shows
something gone wrong is
your head on wrong throw
up it's already here's something on
which you can really pride yes you've
discovered that you can look inside
yourself through you know what that
means thier promoted through no longer
a few run out thread member
a poem you want to read through I it's
a camera it's a thought pose like
a film that could retain the images that
light so secretly through your brain have
you ever tried to see the shadow world
inside photographed by the retina and held
suspended in its memory through this
is one of the more unusual talents
and it's yours it seems to think maybe
this will revive your bank balance three
members think everybody drink
you think you can look inside
yourself you can look inside anyone
thirsty much thinner so many
one can't count the thoughts of the
population of the world for almost two full
potential of two billion
customers all with
a dream to one tank figured out
a new angle get it three days
on the installment plan through
will be in the money man thinks
America just as you were
a complete bust theory had just. Fight
till you're in the chips then watch the
dream girl warm up those chilly lift get
on the phone make us smile financial don't
convert this room and do
a consultation room and go into
business on your own. Call
set up
a business now Joe place refurnished in the
latest style all you need to start you
off by the customer. Opportunity not.
Already. There they are.
This installment on the two billion
climb. Method of treatment don't worry
and uncertain times like the
mammoth don't provide. The
materials at hand. Have
case number one. Don't get.
Case number one Mr and Mrs A Here's
a bank clerk middle income bracket character
thought of exact thrive complained he
has mind like a double entry column thrown
over to throw right through desires
a dream for fun with practical value
to widen his horizon Mission thirty
a raise in salary historical precedents
for this hope range from Jacob's pillow
through Freud kept things as they were
please step outside during interview
thorium and phone Lee one dream to
a customer Thiel free to talk now and
his special interest side of life
and job Thrun thought your idea of private
fun thing pictures out of magazine
Thaksin thoughts find out what the
ME thought he would look for and I
thought this I thought third
thing I think I understand
the need to correct
a gray letter cover you hide the wild images
of the art loving. Memory of mortgages
loans and property sales. And with
a cry the night. Yeah
.
For.
Shane tree. And middle love it can
work a crowd
a night in. Nightingale
and they have ran one
route and carry. Them mad
cow. And mad paws like theirs and wall of.
Fire
and they dragged me into wood to our cabin
in the middle of the street one of them
faith talk about love and pleasure.
Yes I can find. Out on
your bike and we. Hear.
It OK I don't see you. Want. To take you
over to the way I don't
like. To leave it yeah.
You know Leon you know why the
old one was willing to. Hear it.
Majors in
a home. Park. Watching them but it. Was.
Admirable. That you told
the one with the cows.
That it was kind of action.
Yeah. They can. The night
shocked me in the fact. They can. Clip.
Over.
A. Week.
I am.
Yes. Or.
Or.
Known that. National Park in. View.
Or. To calmly
in my life. And
in my.
Mind for. Home for. Me.
A. Lot of the satisfaction the stray
However it is too soon to estimate results
of treatment be whatever you care to
give fifty dollars more
than generous yes the
lie to decide and stay for the transaction
no damn favorites deductable from income
tax yes any time at all drop
in. Now well not mention
a word of this to your wife thank you.
Next come in.
You're.
Face Number two I wonder why
she's consulting you she seems
a healthy well balanced girl what kind
of dream does she want she doesn't want
a dream she wants him to find out
fired up what thought out of her
walk along with you on something fifth
make the clarification of international
patent the twentieth century
that the afternoon make
a clean pamphlet to perpetuate for the
public like me to discourage it in public
life action committee for the abolition of
abolition pro-rata part of the big venue
ation of the democratic that the daughter
of American grandfather the little friend
of ten three for the wave and chapter that
she found is your way and thank you Joy
for you know you don't want to
sign up with anything. That.
You have to belong to something otherwise
how would we ever know who you fire
lighting the day captain to
day. Do you. Find people up
at your game and I show you. How you
maintain your photo how you make
a living then him. And poke think
. She's charming but she'll stop at nothing
before you know it you'll start crying
. You're employed now. The kids
go on Joe do something your professional
reputation that state. Certainly an
unusual case organizational new road to.
If you could only look
deeper. Try it. Well but
two years of trying everything
out of focus on your god.
Taken your. Plate away most of you do
thank you I believe getting to the.
Point for sure to give.
My didn't take
a nap to. Practice being
that if you believe in life and how he
maintains Now think about how you make.
Sure you can get by Mark Probert however
before he found out that. The Met.
All right. I never dotted line what's
the difference you'll never belong to
anything anyway you don't have to take no.
Heed to your prom matter.
Caught and you know.
Well borne out on the phone oh Vina was
born out of breath. But to God it would be
a great day if that them build
up on the heavenly leader was.
I'm. Now do you really want born as it
proper. For
a proportion what plan she went forth from
the mold to take with it and forward and
she grew up on touch if I.Q.
Than. I am I knew.
Chromium nerved and her platinum brain work
chafed me in case I didn't fellow pain
and to top off
a daughter by and found she was
eclipsed with prefabricated far
was. If repairs from
life. Happened. There
I am find my no matter who
would love make it look.
Fortune that I. Am. My.
Only. For I am
for my. Cry for my maid.
Brought my heart broken leg
a parent. Or friend be done made it right.
Then just like the movies a mail order
a mail sent by the God direct from
jail he was and I'm with that they
feel let me be what Rich
and his love for her was.
Right basically what I did didn't knock
at her door but love that right. For
evermore they were made for each other
exclusively planned so he bent his ante
after our. Marriage.
Was.
For a bridal gown look at it leave
a milf and find under
a common pressure or in. For
us there are
a lot of flower is expensive and it's been
very frightened when they'll be painting
rebirth. Singing songs with
woot as they plan to prove
it in the Sunday.
You know fanciful dreams out it or you
doing here and there going you know
we're going to your brain out. To
prove they can move in harmony
with.
Nature and I will not winter.
Here with Diamond and.
Very. Practical things
that appeal to the mind of
a healthy. Own
nature and not when. I apply with.
Upraised it may. Fact
become. That appeal to my.
Master I plan I've always dreamed of
this moment in time which would be nice
dodging to see about marital bliss
with the glorious picnic of
a few I suppose expensive and I do
have a half year's eve rocketed as
a full featured term of
a turkey too much in my time watch my new
club of oh well I suppose and don't make
such
a fuss raised. Kind patchouli
terrorist leaders we. Take
your. Gift to come to my aid.
To the passing bad boy they
had right to write a play
a bigger. Fish
.
We thought of turning him. Head off the.
Rack and you would be both and they
might melt if they fell and M O
O O breath and brightness and he
fell to the ground. Right in life there.
You write. That down on and on and on as.
I read only the word.
Good and all had to be
a Who prepared to meet had been
a one day. Head on with the
trip. Her groom. Much later.
Did Go been through the
then bit in the great if
that was so she ride on
through the evening and your ashy
bright that's. All that no man I
could ever. Build it for fabric
a car. Oh
I.
Was was five
and she rides through the
evening I feel rash he was.
Father's no man on.
Fire Girl with free fruit
a few. Brewing.
For.
Fun
fun. Fun
.
Against your better judgment what's happening
to the jumpy all the time and all of
that and today have even noticed I'm
sure well can you expect to get
a man like that you stand for something
in your many activities attended
responsibility to the community and why
they're all over this empty feeling and
what it's like living in
a vacuum day after day running the house
all it's just right in the neck not
getting to the droning voice
of his life to him that's
a fact and then you try to flee to earth
and turn the thing to do with irritating
little. Under the theme of the world with
closing in on you crushing you in five am
and you hear me dogs barking at the moon
and somebody with that echoing in the
street oh it's terrible and you told
him. And you copy coffee that's why you
get onto curiosity maybe men can tell
you were to opt out he offered to give.
You know this man is obviously
a big fake of some guy and anyway now
you're here you might as well find out what
if game is Heaven's what any of my friends
knew I'd been here no reason they should
by now all right you're invited Nala
down with. I want to thank me the same
as my husband was given of course are
you interested in my phantom call. By
Shorty I hope it won't take long whatever
it is hate to hear what its record about
living off of the feeding of the liturgy
doesn't inspire confidence what you
photograph Why should you give me probably
want to see my reaction why don't you
scream at a movie aloud in town and you
don't have any reactions you are living in
a ship that. Although it is
interesting to the girl which
reminds me of myself when I
was with her his last in
a million lunches tease than if it's Janet
he's made. A member of the interim and
now this Nancy that. Died zero point
one zero to the poems he needed to.
Acca don't break it into deep space get
into deep break in it break it into the
tree if. By forbearing one
I. Find
a breasted are going up along it by an
operation hiding all but haven't been it's
based repaired
a bed from which I shall be born. But
you look at me as if I were some.
Strange light refuses to assimilate himself
to your milieu where you know perfectly
well that you can be as easily seduced by
an exotic Prince as by one of your own
you know. You're a friend
or the cliques like
a metronome within the space limits to
which risking the same destruction the
button. I left with.
Only in risk as an escape us. Those who
have assured themselves against all risks
are bound to lose all.
Your.
Buddy. We are going to have the privilege
tonight of witnessing one of the most
unusual don't have
a preview that ever it may lack in the way
of found in common you make the plot out
of your own conversation and are
looking at me back. For the
real think that the presentation.
Honestly implore you to collaborate even
more actively You all know the
principal character in the film
you have every confidence in him and in
the economy of gesture to give these
gestures their full meaning. And is the
request you to follow and to repeat.
As they have there are we agreed.
That Thank you. If.
The.
Four zero zero zero zero zero zero zero
zero zero zero zero zero zero zero zero
zero zero.
zero Zero zero
. If.
If. For.
A time. You see it's like the school.
People look at one side that's pretty but
a more closely tied subject matter of country
of origin language but look carefully
at the other side and you would see the
real significance tutti the exact date the
right.
Funny comments map. And
if we're not and don't
fight my name please. I'll pay in cash for
bar fight.
With the dog get over there sit
down. What's on his
mind like an emergency case.
Do something not exactly your line Joe.
Twenty But he went on like streams and cut
should be
a snap. So they are. Amazing. Now
what.
A light. By. The customer is always right
is the problem. He has no
conscience for has no subconscious
facts why he wants to have
a drink foul that there's
a paradox Why should an extrovert
a man of action like this customer need
your services maybe there's something to
this brain wreck Fabian dream can't tip off
who's going to win the Derby this year
it won't find
a bad few wants what he wants what he
wants the family how can you look into
somebody who won't relax.
Well that's one way to
relax thank you very much Sam
Ok Bob you'll get what you
ask for. Help at work.
From. Home.
From.
The.
Imagine an active type
like that having such
a delicate drink that wasn't so much
of an extra thirty might have been
a problem. Not tips for the right path.
But you hand me
a lot of Dave's thought. A
waste of my time by. Me
business is business what I got it.
That I license.
Test.
It.
What it is then prize going to play to.
The.
From.
An.
Mom.
From. Our.
Private practice had to bat it
at that. Now a blind man and
a child. Your
dreamed
a lot I want to tell you what
amounted I have so many.
The open.
Long.
If the fields. So they are grandpa who.
You're. Fed by.
Are you waiting for me.
More.
From.
Home.
I was born much was said about. It was
a tragic car laughing down the street the
time my father in the good living hours
was a normal family I'm a normal man of
a dock of average size and with excellent
teeth if you study my teeth he would know
me for my hand I have
a leg that I will suddenly
the biggest load response of
not enough one day we must all
face the great fear that.
Were.
You. Were
with.
Him one day in May suddenly
happen I met myself
I was not prepared for it when and speak
probably came to my senses were not I
don't nothing I said nothing that I
tried to reason it out blue why is
blue worse than green violet or white I
don't know why that isn't violent green or
blue I'm just. I'm.
Whatever it is you're
a treat India. It is the final
retreat that makes everything. In
the newspaper your dot com Your
wife will you know work in my
I've always been
a decent law abiding citizen have
across the street against the might.
Of the light. Yes but who would you
want to sit at the same table with
a Blue Man your dojo friend oh right i am
i wouldn't go so far no you wouldn't as
you know are not blue No I don't like it
Joe I know Joe Biden is Dana glad lyeth
thrown back into the ocean what the
heck he doing it out that I'm not
a seller from South sorry
but you have to leave
a curate. They
left me alone. In the cold. Even
familiar objects became friends.
I had always thought they had
a private life of them.
Help me. Know how. It was only.
Everything with cope with
life no calling on my part.
I tried to figure out what had happened
in an emergency and there are things you
can count on the metronome in yourself
on mother's piano sound of the big clock
over the mantel piece the repeated agonies
of love the invasion of Holland May
tenth nine hundred forty five situation
became clear because everything else became
so unclear the blue thread of hope will
lead me out of the latter fight to
have
a mom I had to go at so I did. Why
. Why.
Why.
Where do you think you're going to eat out
that mess just as bad today no room for
competition restrictions are you have to
be imposed on the opposite of all the
right of big and everybody why of the
right of every right have left right and
right to right or wrong their out of right
or out of wrong the right to walk you
don't like they have somebody over the
head because they watch is own way aid. Or
you may lose your way altogether whether
you think you're going east west south not
.
Good luck have
a good trip. The
war is over I'll take
a vacation to play go every day
of the. Funny though you are
still on. The paycheck every Friday night
T.V.
. Don't make couple forget about
your politics or your religion. I
suddenly realized I had lost my way and
I caught one thing behind me nothing in
front of. Every not every.
Play.
Yes yes.
Oh.
Oh. Oh.
oh Oh.
Oh
.
Iggy.
If
Sure if we were always getting involved
if there's no way of not getting involved
if there seemed
a way out if yes to start all
over again all over again if
all over if returned to forgotten
memories are the faces of the old
guard shining excited if inspired
that if leaving unforgettable
traces enter my make up your mind
maybe it's better this way for only
time safe enjoy your friend if
the same room same chance to sit on the
same car if it we are again just like an
old time. Turn on the radio
or face conversation.
With. Everything the same sure
only you are not the same.
For all time. Look closely at the
objective. Eighteen different.
They are the people. You will want.
It over with not forget. Many men and have
a compromise or gone into business on
a small say. What the use
of a roof with bottom
a house. Don't do the emergency
I was forced to choose
a way out I did not like my mind was made
up my back it was ready for the job I had
delayed much all kinds of events passed
through my mind some of them happened long
ago I remember them without any
apparent order or significance I
remember that I went with my second wife
to the thief on photo was taken. When
discovered a new star in the southern
sky and I saw a dear old Ollie in
a kind of B.F.
Of the world went to pieces in the pieces
lived on separate problem I came from or
all events isolated needed everything
seemed to happen at once and in the same
state it was quite
a new experience then I decided to tear
up my one way if they were I was fine
I had not come so far only to jump
a foot long moment I would not for
the great embarrassment and I liked
I would have gone on anyway no matter what
happened there is so much ahead of. How
much I have to find.
The phone.